MONA Jiravirotekul

Email: cooleye4@yahoo.com | LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/mona-jiravirotekul-26347768/ Portfolio: https://monaesthetician.github.io/ | GitHub: https://github.com/monaesthetician| Cell: (513) 429-6322

Entry level Web Developer

More than 10 years of experience in marketing and sales in the advertising industry. Passionate about aesthetic composition and eager to learn new information. Worked with graphic designer and art directors as a part of a team to complete projects before deadline. Self-motivated web developer seeking an opportunity to assist a new team to succeed.

Technical Skills

- HTML
- CSS3
- Java script

- M.E.R.N Stack
- GitHub
- React-Redux

- SQL
- MongoDB

Experience

April 2017- Present

Server, Ban Thai Restaurant

Cincinnati, Ohio

- Provide excellent customer services.
- Greet customers and presents menus.
- Make suggestions based on their preference.
- Take and serve food/drinks orders.
- Up-sell when appropriate.
- Arrange table settings.
- Keep tables and dining room clean and tidy at all times.
- Deliver checks and collect payments.

January 2013 - July 2014

Account Executive, Money channel

Bangkok, Thailand

- Assisting in the development of sales presentations and marketing materials.
- Developed and manage revenue producing relationships with client and agencies.
- Provided consultation to sales managers, sales teams and clients.
- Provided clients with convergent selling, to package several broadcast and online products.
- Other responsibilities as assigned by manager.

June 2011 - March 2013

Retail Sales Associate, King power

Bangkok, Thailand

- Maintained organized, presentable merchandise to drive continuous sales.
- Assisting customers with finding alternative merchandise to meet needs.
- Organized racks and shelves to maintain store visual appeal, engage customers and promote specific merchandise.
- Participating company training opportunities as the company offers.

April 2004 - September 2008

Account Executive, Q Advertising

Bangkok, Thailand

- Sold print advertising.
- Worked positively and productively with the production team and finance department to provide clients and agencies satisfaction.
- Worked independently and collaboratively with multiple departments (internally & externally) to ensure opportunities for revenue growth are maximized.
- Worked collaboratively with internal partners to drive revenue.
- Followed all station procedures for preparing orders, resolving billing issues, submitting regular reports regarding sales, forecasts and competitive analysis.

April 2001 - August 2004

Customer Service, Inspire Image

Bangkok, Thailand

- Obtained client information by answering telephone calls; interviewing clients; verifying information.
- Established policies by entering client information to requirements.
- Informed clients by explaining procedures; answering questions; providing information.
- Maintained communication equipment by reporting problems.
- Maintained and improves quality results by adhering to standards; recommending improved procedures.
- Updated job knowledge by studying new product

Education

Kable Academy • March - June 2021

Web Development

Aveda Fedric's Institute • February 2020 - August 2021

Esthiology

Waltham Forest College • 2014-2015

English for Speaker of Other Languages (ESOL)

Westminster Kingsway College • 2015-2016

English for Speaker of Other Languages (ESOL)

Bachelors of arts \bullet Sripatum University \bullet 1995 - 1999

Communication arts, Advertising

Cincinnati, Ohio

Cincinnati, Ohio

London, UK

London, UK

Bangkok, Thailand